ADDY: We do a whole lot of mobile web development, right?
我们在开发移动网络方面做了大量工作，对吧？
MATT: Yes.
是的
ADDY: And it's important to be properly cross device testing
在多台设备上进行测试很重要
stuff so it looks beautiful, and it's fast and performant
因此，它看起来不错，快速且性能适当。
and everything.
我们尝试。
There are a lot of tools involved in that.
有很多工具可以使用。
So what do you use?
那你用什么呢？
MATT: There are lots of tools out there.
那里有很多工具。
What I use though is probably a bad example.
尽管如此，我使用的还是一个不好的例子。
Like, I think one of my main issues
我认为我的主要问题之一
is a lot of these tools are really hard to just get set up
这些工具中有很多真的很难安装
and working all together and just happy.
轻松解决。
So for me, I use Browsersync, but I'm really
对我来说，使用Browsersync
heavily relying on DevTools like the Device Emulation Mode.
但是我严重依赖DevTools之类的Explain Device Simulator。
And I'm still doing the browser wobbling
我仍然测试了浏览器
backwards and forwards.
在各方面。
ADDY: Device Mode has got presets
设备模式具有预设
for all the devices in there.
对于所有现有设备
MATT: I know, but the problem is like DevTools takes up
我知道，但是问题是DevTools正在运行
x amount of space, and then you've got--
一定的空间，那么您就可以
ADDY: This is what you've got to like--
那就是你要做的
so I've got a second monitor specifically for my full screen
我有第二个屏幕专门用于全屏模式
DevTools, and you can--
在DevTools中，您可以-
MATT: Yeah, but then I need a second monitor.
是的，但是我需要第二个屏幕。
Like I do a lot of it just on my laptop, nothing else.
因为我只是在笔记本电脑上做很多工作。
So I get what you mean, though.
所以我明白你的意思了。
Like if I could just stick to Device Mode, I would.
例如，如果您可以承诺放置设备，则可以。
But DevTools just doesn't mung well with me
但是DevTools与我的配合不好
in my head in Device Mode on this one screen.
在我的脑海中，在一个屏幕上处于设备模式。
ADDY: Yeah.
是的
MATT: That's the only thing.
-那是唯一的。 -看起来像什么
could be doing better.
我们可以做得更好。
So I use BrowserStack pretty heavily.
因此，主要使用BrowserStack。
It's great for just-- so BrowserStack
非常适合-BrowserStack
is like a cloud-based service where
被认为是基于云的服务
you've got a subscription.
您有订阅的地方。
And you can just fire off URLs and open them up
您可以打开URL链接
in different OSs, different mobile devices.
在几个操作系统上，不同的移动设备。
Here I've got like my site loaded up
我在这里我的网站已经上传
on iOS on an iPhone 6 Plus.
在适用于iPhone 6 Plus的iOS上。
And I can control the device.
而且我可以控制机器。
I can navigate on here.
我可以从这里导航。
It's not just a static screenshot,
这不仅仅是静态屏幕截图，
so it's actually pretty useful.
实际上，它非常有用。
And I find BrowserStack pretty useful.
我还发现BrowserStack非常有用。
It's got support for screenshots and all that stuff.
支持屏幕截图和所有这些东西。
MATT: I've found BrowserStack to be really useful when
我发现BrowserStack在以下方面真的很有用
you want to do manual testings.
通过手动测试。
So literally, you're making changes-- especially when
因此，从字面上看，您正在进行更改-尤其是当
you do local host tunneling.
您隧道传输到本地主机。
You can just make local changes.
您只能进行本地更改。
It's almost immediately back on the emulator.
它将在模拟器上显示。
You can scroll around, and it's great for, like I say,
您可以滚动内容，很好订购
manual testing.
手动测试。
I've used Saucelabs where I've actually created scripts
我在创建实际脚本的地方使用了Saucelabs
to literally just take screenshots of it,
要仅捕获她的屏幕截图，
run simple tests like how long it takes pages to load,
然后运行快速测试，例如加载页面需要多长时间，
different things like that.
诸如此类。
And that was quite a while ago that I did that.
这已经有点长了。
Like now you've got things like web page test
现在有东西网页测试
for performance and everything.
测试性能和一切。
But Saucelabs seems like it's more geared towards automation
但是Saucelabs配备了更多功能，可以使测试更加自动化。
ADDY: Yeah, so we use Saucelabs for things
是的，所以我们将Saucelabs用于类似
like continuous integration.
持续集成。
So say you've got [? a per ?] request
假设您有东西
that you want to make sure works across all your target
您想确保它能在所有浏览器上正常工作
browsers.
您的目标。
Saucelabs is perfect for just nailing that use case.
在这种情况下，Saucelabs是完美的。
BrowserStack's really good, I think,
我认为Saucelabs非常好，
if you're working on personal projects.
如果您正在处理个人项目。
And there are people that use BrowserStack in sort of a CI
有人在使用BrowserStack
setup as well with Selenium.
与Selenium中一样，已安装CI。
What else?
还有什么
MATT: So I never used to use Browsersync because--
我以前从未使用过Browsersync，因为-
ADDY: And then you met me, and your life was better.
然后我们见面，你的生活变得更好
MATT: No.
没有。
I learned about Browsersync because of you.
我从您那里了解Browsersync。
But the thing that you never told to me
可是你从没告诉过我
was that you-- so when you're in the Gulp file,
那是您-当您进入Gulp文件时，
you can actually just define a proxy for Browsersync
您只能为Browsersync指定代理
to actually go through.
一起工作。
ADDY: At some point, I expect you to read--
在某个时候，我希望您阅读-
MATT: It's never going to happen, Addy.
上瘾不会发生。
It's never going to happen.
它永远不会发生。
Why do you think we keep on doing this?
您为什么认为我们会继续这样做？
So you can define a proxy, which in this case,
您可以指定代理，在这种情况下
I just say the proxy is local host.
我可以说他是当地的房东。
And then what happens is I can have an Nginx server,
然后我得到了Nginx服务器，
and then Browsersync will create a separate port.
然后，Browsersync将创建一个单独的端口。
And it will just inject the JavaScript
JavaScript将进入
that Browsersync needs to work, which you never told me about.
该Browsersync需要正常工作，但这并没有告诉我
So I've only just learned about it,
我一个人学的
but it means that now I can have the devices like this
这意味着我可以得到这样的设备
and it'll sync scrolls.
滚动将同步。
It'll sync touches.
触摸将同步。
It does whatever I tell it to do, and that's like awesome.
您可以按照我的要求做，这太好了。
And yeah, it's just any visual changes
是的，没有明显的变化
that I make in terms of code, it will just reload,
代码映像中的最新映像将被重新加载，
and it will just happen, which is really, really nice.
它将发生，这很酷。
Because you have devices like this on your desk,
因为您的桌子上有这样的设备，
or I even have a couple of browsers
甚至我有几个浏览器
just on my desktop machine running,
在我的电脑上工作
and I can just do any kind of commands on here, any actions,
我可以在这里执行任何命令
and it's just matched across all the browsers or all
它将应用于所有浏览器
the devices.
或硬件。
ADDY: Yeah, Browsersync's awesome.
是的，Browsersync很棒。
I think we covered it in another episode,
我想我们在另一集中谈论过
but it's also got this really nice UI
但它也有一个非常好的用户界面
for configuring network throttling,
要设置网络路由器，
configuring do you want it to sync clicks and forms
设置是否同步点击和配置
and scrolls and all that other stuff.
并滚动浏览所有这些东西。
So Browsersync's probably my favorite cross device testing
因此，Browsersync通常是跨设备测试工具
tool, I'd say.
我的最爱
The other thing that we use pretty heavily,
我们经常使用的另一件事
it's just like regular old VM setup.
就像旧版安装的虚拟机VM。
So some people use VirtualBox.
有些人使用VirtualBox。
I use VMware.
我使用VMware。
But it's really nice being able to easily fire up
能够轻松运行旧版本真是太好了
old versions of VMs with IE and Edge
带有IE和Edge浏览器的虚拟机
and all those other things on them.
还有他们身上的所有东西。
MATT: Yeah, I don't have a Windows machines,
是的，我没有Windows设备，
so I pretty much rely on the VMware images--
所以我完全依靠VMware虚拟版本-
well, sorry, the VirtualBox images-- because for me,
抱歉，复制VirtualBox-因为对我来说，
it's much easier than using something like BrowserStack
这比将某些内容用作BrowserStack要容易得多
or Saucelabs when I want to do a quick test to do it locally.
当我想在本地进行快速测试时，请选择Saucelabs。
It works a little bit better, in my opinion.
我认为效果更好。
And it's the same with emulators for mobile devices,
与移动模拟器相同
especially Safari's, the iOS emulator
特定于Safari（iOS模拟器）
is really, really good.
真的很好。
Android, eh, not so much, but you know.
Android并不多，但您知道。
ADDY: So actually, there's something
真的有事
that I came across when I was in Tokyo recently.
我最近在东京时发现了他。
And it's a tool that's been in development for two years.
已经开发了两年的工具。
And it kind of blows the water out
他们有点
of any other cross device testing thing for Android.
它将崩溃任何适用于Android的跨设备测试工具。
MATT: Yeah.
是的
ADDY: I think it's called Open STF.
我认为它叫做Open STF。
It's by two guys that work at CyberAgent.
由两个为Cyber​​Agent工作的年轻人开发。
It basically is the kitchen sink for mobile device testing.
它是移动设备的测试盆。
It gives you this really beautiful visual catalog
您拥有出色的视觉指标
of all the devices you've connected up.
对于您已连接的所有设备。
You can easily control them.
您可以轻松控制它们。
Are you familiar with DevTools Screencasting feature?
您对DevTools中的数字屏幕显示功能有想法吗？
MATT: Yes.
是的
ADDY: So this basically does that,
主要是他所做的
but for all these other devices you plugged in.
但对于所有连接的设备。
So DevTools Screencast is great for a single device.
DevTools中屏幕的数字显示非常适合一台设备。
This is great for like a multitude of them,
这对其中几个人来说真是太棒了
where you want to set up a device lab.
您要在其中安装硬件实验室的位置。
MATT: And this is very much like-- I always
这很像-我一直
see this as like a supplement to something like Browsersync
我认为这是对Browsersync之类的补充
because this basically helps you control all the devices
它主要有助于控制所有设备
in terms of launching the browser
关于运行浏览器
and pointing them to a particular URL, which
并将它们定向到特定的URL，
is the one bit that I hate about all of this.
这是我唯一讨厌的事情。
And it's pretty much all I've ever
总的来说我是做什么的
done with the many mobile device lab stuff with Pete LePage.
Pete LePage的移动实验室。
That entire focus is how do I launch a browser with this URL?
所有这些都集中于如何使用此URL运行浏览器？
And it seems that they've basically taken that
看来他们拿走了
and then just put it on steroids and made
他们让他兴奋剂
it ridiculously awesome.
所以变得很棒
ADDY: This is just the best thing ever.
那是有史以来最好的事情。
It's so, so awesome.
这很酷。
MATT: So I guess we just need to go set it up.
我认为我们需要安装它。
ADDY: Yeah, I definitely want to get the set up in Google.
是的，绝对要在Google上安装它。
And there's a lot of people that would benefit from it.
许多人将从中受益。
MATT: No, no, no, we're going to keep this for ourselves.
不，不，我们会为我们保留它。
ADDY: Just ourselves, nobody else.
只有我们，没有其他人。
MATT: No one else can touch it-- never.
没有人会碰它。